THABANG LETHEBE LESETEDI

P.O BOX 10351 LOBATSE

MOBILE PHONE: 76366271

E-MAIL: lethebe.lesetedi@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A dedicated professional with 5+ years of experience and a zest to become one of the leading accountants in the industry. A true professional who is curious for knowledge and always prioritizing learning opportunities. I aim to attain a suitable position that will allow me to apply my knowledge and experience by overseeing responsibilities in line with problem solving, planning, budget organizing, which will ultimately derive results.

CORE SKILL

- SAGE ACCPACC
- Pastel Accounting System
- GAAP
- Risk Identification & Management
- Microsoft Office Applications
- Sage Pastel & Sage Evolution
- Data Analysis
- Business Analysis

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administration and Accounts Officer at Distron Pty Ltd (March 2014 - December 2019)

Responsibilities

- Assets register management.
- Preparing statements of financial position and of comprehensive income
- Creditors and debtors reconciliation
- Managing telephone System(Man3000), CCTV
- Supervision of warehouse personnel
- Updating of staff records and relevant administration documentation
- Stock Control, Receiving, Purchasing, Stock GRV
- Update financial records with recent transactions and changes
- Management of accounts receivables and payables
- Reconciling processed work by verifying expense reports and comparing system reports to balance

• Scheduling and ensuring vendor payments

Temporary Contracts Administrator at G4S Security Systems (September 2011 - December 2011)

Responsibilities

- Ensured on the timely execution and completion of contracts
- Negotiate terms and conditions
- Analyze and mitigate risk
- Develop company contracts

Accounting Trainee at Francistown Toyota (September 2010-November 2010)

Responsibilities

- Daily Reconciliation of Accounts receivables, payables and monthly deposits with station attendants
- Reconciliation of daily taking from the service station store
- Ensuring payments are filled out appropriately and on time
- Preparation and updating cash book expenses as well as monthly income statements

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

2016	INSURANCE INSTITUTE OF SOUTH AFRICA (IISA)
	Certificate of Proficiency (C.O.P) – Basic of Long Term Insurance
2012-2014	Chartered Institute of Management Accountants "CIMA"
	Diploma in Management Accounting
2009-2011	Botswana Accountancy College
	Association of Accounting Technicians (AAT)
2007-2008	Gaborone Senior Secondary School
	Botswana General Certificate of Secondary Education Obtained results: 39 points
	BGCSE

ADDITIONAL ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS

- 2008 Botswana National Open Debate Champions
- 2008 Monash Open Debate Runners-up

REFERENCES

NAME: Gosego Monyake

COMPANY: Distron Botswana

DESIGNATION: Business Development Manager

CONTACT: +267 74135173

Email: gosegom@distron.co.bw

NAME: Ravi Angara

COMPANY: Distron Botswana

DESIGNATION: Business Development Manager

CONTACT: +267 72331866

Email: ravia@distron.co.bw

PREPARED BY: Thabang L. Lesetedi

NAME: Akash Sharma

COMPANY: Distron Botswana

DESIGNATION: Finance Manager

CONTACT: +267 7558044

Email: akashs@distron.co.bw